Guide to the Cornell Women's Club of New York Records, 1910-1973
Cornell Women's Club of New York Records, 1910-1973
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell Women's Club of New York Records, 1910-1973
41-6-1674
Cornell Women's Club of New York.
3.7 cubic ft.
Correspondence, publicity notices, newsletters, brochures, a handbook, minutes, programs, and other materials.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes correspondence; materials related to the Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs; material on parties given for new graduates; publicity notices for social events; newsletters; brochures and other material related to art tours; officers handbook; minutes of meetings; history of the club; and programs of the Cornell Women's Club of New York.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes correspondence; materials related to the Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs; material on parties given for new graduates; publicity notices for social events; newsletters; brochures and other material related to art tours; officers handbook; minutes of meetings; history of the club; and programs of the Cornell Women's Club of New York.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell Women's Club of New York.; Cornell University--Alumni and alumnae.; Cornell University--Societies, etc.; Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs.
Subjects:
Women--Societies and clubs.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Minutes, 1900-1918 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Minutes, 1911-1928 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Minutes, 1919-1926 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Minutes, 1927-1933 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Minutes, 1931-1935 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Minutes, 1936-1937 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Minutes, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Minutes, correspondence, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Minutes, 1940-1942 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Minutes, newsletters, etc., 1943-1948 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Minutes, 1949-1952 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Minutes, 1953-1957 (Box 1, Folder 12-13)
- Report of the committee appointed by the Cornell Alumni of New York to investigate conditions at Sage College, 1907 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Leases with Hotel Barbizon, Inc., 1927-1936 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Leases with Hotel Barbizon, Inc., 1937-1942 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Leases with Hotel Barbizon, Inc., 1944-1948 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Leases with Hotel Barbizon, Inc., 1949-1953 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Leases with Hotel Barbizon, Inc., correspondence, 1930-1948 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Hotel Barbizon: sub-tenants' agreements, 1934-1948 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Interest Committee, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Fields of work, book 4, 1938-1940 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Fields of work, book 4, 1938-1940 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Fields of work, book 3 (clippings), 1937-1941 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Fields of work, book 2 (clippings), 1933-1942 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Fields of work, book 2 (clippings), 1938-1941 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Fields of work, book 1, 1938-1949 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Fields of work, book 1, 1935-1942 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Fields of work, conference book 1, 1937-1941 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Constitution, 1947-1956 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Nominating Committee, 1935-1955 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Alumni Trustee, 1954-1955 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Placement, 1957-1959 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- General correspondence, 1953-1954 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Correspondence, 1957-1957 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Receipted bills, 1949-1951 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Bank statements and cancelled checks, 1951-1953 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Financial statements, 1953-1954 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Financial statements, 1953-1954 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Bills and receipts, 1952-1953 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Vouchers, 1953-1955 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Financial records, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Treasurer's records, 1948-1955 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Constitutional Revision Committee, 1949-1954 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Annual - Special Reports, 1932-1956 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Correspondence, 1955-1956 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Publicity, 1941-1955 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Mailings and publicity, 1953-1957 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Mailing permits, etc., 1953-1954 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Inventories, 1955-1956 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Miscellaneous, 1949-1962 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Miscellaneous, 1955-1956 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Annual luncheon, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Annual luncheon, 1939-1940 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Annual luncheon, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Annual luncheon, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Annual luncheon, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Annual luncheon, 1943-1945 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Annual luncheon, 1943-1951 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Annual luncheon, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Annual luncheon, c. 1946-1954 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Annual luncheon, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Annual luncheon, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Annual luncheon, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Annual luncheon, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Annual luncheon, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Annual luncheon, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Annual luncheon, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Annual luncheon, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Annual luncheon, 1956-1960 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Annual luncheon, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Annual luncheon, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Annual luncheon, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Annual luncheon, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Annual luncheon, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Annual luncheon, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Servicemen's parties, 1942-1944 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Cornell Chorus, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Card party, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- "Flahooley"- theatre party, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Theatre party, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Glee Club concert, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- A Cappella concert, 1949-1953 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Freshman parties and lists, 1950-1953 (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Theatre benefits, "Flahooley", 1951 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Cornell boat trip, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Report on "Another Night of Chance", 1953 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Report on "Another Night of Chance", 1953 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- The Cornell Cooler, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Night of Chance and card party, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Night of Chance, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Theatre benefit "All Summer Long", 1955 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Benefit, 1955-1956 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Benefit, 1956-1957 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Welcome to Class ' 57 - ' 62, 1957-1963 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Cornell Dinner, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Money-raising suggestions, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 13)
- President's correspondence, 1959-1963 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- History of the Cornell Women's Club of NY, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Cornell Women's Club -- Women's City Club, 1955-1960 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- First Art Tour, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Second Art Tour, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Third Art Tour, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Third Art Tour, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Fourth Art Tour, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Fifth Art Tour, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Sixth Art Tour, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Board of Directors meeting minutes and financial records, 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Board of Directors meeting minutes, etc, 1957-1958 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Patricia Carry, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Patricia Carry, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Patricia Carry, 1965-1967 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Correspondence, etc., 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Program, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Correspondence, etc., 1969-1971 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Meetings, programs, etc., 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Correspondence, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Correspondence, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Correspondence, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Correspondence, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Correspondence and publicity, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Biographical records, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Nursing School, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Treasurer, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- Lists -- Class of 1892-1956 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Letter, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Membership lists, 1934-1956 (Box 3, Folder 44)
- Membership, 1953-1954 (Box 3, Folder 45)
- Membership, 1955-1956 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Paid members, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Membership, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Membership, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Boat ride, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Miscellaneous, 1960-1962 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Federation benefit, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Printing sample, 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Printing, publicity, meeting notices, 1959-1968 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Printing, publicity, meeting notices, 1959-1967 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Printing, notices, 1955-1972 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Bulk mailing (pamphlets), n.d. (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Miscellaneous scrapbook material (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Miscellaneous scrapbook material (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Officers' handbook, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Membership directories, etc., 1909-1966 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Cornell Women's Club announcement and printed letter "To Cornell Alumnae", 1910, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Cornell Alumnae Club scrapbook, 1900-1920 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Scrapbook, 1925-1930 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Scrapbook, 1930-1933 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Scrapbook, 1933-1938 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Scrapbook, 1938-1939 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Scrapbook, 1939-1940 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Scrapbook, 1940-1942 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Woman at Work: A Tour Among Careers, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- So Brief a Span: poems by Lewette Pollock Pierce (' 14), 1938 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Autographed letters
  - Marie Powers, Aug. 24, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Franchot Tone, Apr. 4, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Joyce D. Brothers, June 10, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Hendrik Van Loon, Nov. 15, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Thomas E. Dewey, Nov. 9, 1945, Jan. 16, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - E. B. White, May 12, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Charles Collingwood, Feb. 19, 1947, Jan. 13, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Kenneth Roberts, Jan. 17, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Adolphe Menjou, July 1, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Frank Sullivan, Dec. 26, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Perle Mesta, Oct. 23, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 32)